import Questions from './questions';

const mediumMath = new Questions([
    // Add two 3 digit numbers
    {
        question: 'What is 461 + 806?',
        answer: 1267,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 781 + 176?',
        answer: 957,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 851 + 540?',
        answer: 1391,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 313 + 296?',
        answer: 609,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 111 + 334?',
        answer: 445,
    },
    // Subtract a 3-digit number from any whole thousand
    {
        question: 'Fill in the blank: 5,000 – _ = 4,306.',
        answer: 694,
    },
    {
        question: 'Fill in the blank: 9,000 – _ = 8,873.',
        answer: 127,
    },
    {
        question: 'Fill in the blank: 6,000 – _ = 5,554.',
        answer: 446,
    },
    {
        question: 'Fill in the blank: 3,000 – _ = 2,379.',
        answer: 621,
    },
    {
        question: 'Fill in the blank: 8,000 – _ = 7,662.',
        answer: 338,
    },
    // Multiple of 7
    {
        question: 'What is 1 x 7?',
        answer: 7,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2 x 7?',
        answer: 14,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 3 x 7?',
        answer: 21,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 4 x 7?',
        answer: 28,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5 x 7?',
        answer: 35,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 6 x 7?',
        answer: 42,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 7 x 7?',
        answer: 49,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 8 x 7?',
        answer: 56,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 9 x 7?',
        answer: 63,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10 x 7?',
        answer: 70,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 11 x 7?',
        answer: 77,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 12 x 7?',
        answer: 84,
    },
    // Multiple of 8
    {
        question: 'What is 1 x 8?',
        answer: 8,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2 x 8?',
        answer: 16,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 3 x 8?',
        answer: 24,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 4 x 8?',
        answer: 32,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5 x 8?',
        answer: 40,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 6 x 8?',
        answer: 48,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 7 x 8?',
        answer: 56,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 8 x 8?',
        answer: 64,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 9 x 8?',
        answer: 72,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10 x 8?',
        answer: 80,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 11 x 8?',
        answer: 88,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 12 x 8?',
        answer: 96,
    },
    // Multiple of 9
    {
        question: 'What is 1 x 9?',
        answer: 9,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2 x 9?',
        answer: 18,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 3 x 9?',
        answer: 27,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 4 x 9?',
        answer: 36,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5 x 9?',
        answer: 45,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 6 x 9?',
        answer: 54,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 7 x 9?',
        answer: 63,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 8 x 9?',
        answer: 72,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 9 x 9?',
        answer: 81,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10 x 9?',
        answer: 90,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 11 x 9?',
        answer: 99,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 12 x 9?',
        answer: 108,
    },
    // Divisible by 10
    {
        question: 'What is 240 / 10?',
        answer: 24,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 30 / 10?',
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 880 / 10?',
        answer: 88,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 60 / 10?',
        answer: 6,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 510 / 10?',
        answer: 51,
    },
    // Divisible by whole tens
    {
        question: 'What is 720 / 90?',
        answer: 8,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 630 / 70?',
        answer: 9,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 120 / 60?',
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 480 / 80?',
        answer: 6,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 600 / 60?',
        answer: 10,
    },
    // Order of operations (five digits with two parenthesis - add, subtract)
    {
        question: 'What is (19 – 9) + (17 – 10 – 6)?',
        answer: 11,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 20 + (17 – 2) – (10 + 24)?',
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is (33 – 8) + (38 + 2) – 1?',
        answer: 64,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is (15 + 28) – 17 + (19 – 13) ?',
        answer: 32,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 28 – (8 + 7) – (6 – 5)?',
        answer: 12,
    },
]);

export default mediumMath;
